question_data = [
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "The song &quot;Megalovania&quot; by Toby Fox made its third appearence in the 2015 RPG &quot;Undertale&quot;.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "&quot;Half-Life 2&quot; runs on the Source Engine.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Pac-Man was invented by the designer Toru Iwatani while he was eating pizza.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "In &quot;Super Mario 3D World&quot;, the Double Cherry power-up originated from a developer accidentally making two characters controllable.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "In the game &quot;Subnautica&quot;, a &quot;Spadefish&quot; will attack you.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Ana was added as a new hero for the game Overwatch on July 19th, 2016.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "The Konami Code is known as Up, Up, Down, Down, Left, Right, Right, Left, B, A, Start.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "&quot;Metal Gear Solid 3: Snake Eater&quot; was released in 2004.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "&quot;Sonic the Hedgehog 2&quot; originally was going to have a time travel system.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "In the video game &quot;Splatoon&quot;, the playable characters were originally going to be rabbits instead of squids.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        }
    ]

